{"data":[{"question":"Nora prevented her son from ___ bad friends.","a":"to make","b":"making","c":"made","d":"make","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Prevent somebody from doing something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Thank you for ___ so much help.","a":"give","b":"giving","c":"being giving","d":"being given","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Thank sbd for doing sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Please remember ___ the power before ___ the office.","a":"to turn off, leaving","b":"turn off, leave","c":"turning off, leaving","d":"turning off, leave","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Remember+ V_ing: Remember something which have already happened\/done \n- Remember+ To Verb: Remember to do something (need to be done) \n- Before + Verb_ing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The group of children practice ___ English in a cram school every evening.","a":"to speak","b":"speak","c":"to be speaking","d":"speaking","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Practice doing something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Doris prefers ___ in a bus to ___.","a":"ride, walk","b":"riding, walking","c":"to ride, walking","d":"to ride, to walk","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Structure: Prefer Verb_ing\/sth To Verb_ing \/ sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Jack and Joseph didn't miss ___ the episode of the TV series last night.","a":"to watch","b":"watching","c":"watched","d":"watch","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Miss doing something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"We don't allow ___ in this area.","a":"smoking","b":"to smoke","c":"people to smoking","d":"people smoking","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Advise\/ allow\/ permit\/ recommend + Verb_ing \n- Advise\/ allow\/ permit\/ recommend + object + to V","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Joan regrets ___ hard in college.","a":"not having studied","b":"not to study","c":"having not studied","d":"not study","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Regret+To Verb: Feel regret for something you are going to do \n- Regret + Verb-ing: Feel regret for something already happened \n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Your motorcycle needs ___.","a":"to be oiled","b":"to oil","c":"to being oiling","d":"oil","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Need + To be Past Particple\/ V_ing: if before \"need\" is not person \n- Need + To Verb: If before \"need\" is person ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The elders needs _________ carefully.","a":"looking after","b":"look after","c":"to look after","d":"being looked after","answer":"1","explain":"- Need doing something: need be done","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"}]}